Guide to the Aaron Cometbus Punk and Underground Press Collection, ca. 1977-2013.
Cometbus, Aaron Punk and Underground Press Collection
- Series I. Punk and Underground Press Materials, 1963-2016
  - Other Locations, 1978-2015
    - Titles A-D, 1980-2015
      - Chain Letter, Undated; Kiraly, Andrew; Taylor, Shaun (Box 12, Folder 59)
        No. 1, 4
        Las Vegas, Nevada
      - Chaos Comix, 1990-1992; Chaos, Randy (Box 2, Folder 71)
        No. 18, 20, 23
        British Columbia, Canada; Ontario, Canada
      - Cherry Hill Comics, Undated (Box 12, Folder 60)
        Washington, D.C.
      - Christmas in Lone Pine, 2002; Glicksberg, Katie (Box 2, Folder 72)
      - Cliché, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 73)
        No. 71
        Denmark
      - Codger, Undated; Silly, Mike (Box 12, Folder 61)
        Columbia, Missouri
      - Common Level, 1985-09-1985-10; Longabaugh, Matt (Box 2, Folder 74)
        Jackson, Michigan
      - Communique, Undated (Box 2, Folder 75)
        No. 23
      - Conditioned Response, 1994; Vierling, Benjamin A. (Box 12, Folder 62)
        Nevada City, California
      - Contaminated, 1991; Jane (Box 12, Folder 63)
      - Cool Dry Place, Undated; Davis, Greg (Box 12, Folder 64)
      - Cretin Bull, 1980-1983; the Sister (Box 2, Folder 76)
        Austin, Texas
      - Crude Noise, 2003-01-2004-07; Stern, Meredith (Box 2, Folder 77)
        Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania
      - Cunt-A-Lope, Undated; Cassidy; Sarah (Box 12, Folder 65)
        Byfield, Massachusetts
      - Cuppa Joe, Undated; Rachel; KJ; Rebecca (Box 12, Folder 66)
        Boulder, Colorado
      - Damaged Goods, 1981-01; Hysen, Lyle (Box 2, Folder 78)
        Vol. 1 No. 3 (2 copies)
        Great Neck, New York
      - De Media, 1986-08-29 (Box 12, Folder 67)
        Eeklo, Belgium
      - Dead Llama on a Kaiser, 1984; Stepe, Steve (Box 12, Folder 68)
        East Peoria, Illinois
      - Design Number Eight-Sixteen, 1993; Michelle (Box 12, Folder 69)
        Madison, Wisconsin
      - Desperate Living, 1994-01-1996 (Box 2, Folder 79)
      - Destined for the Eternal Minor Leagues, 1997-06; Zenick, Jeff (Box 2, Folder 80)
        Eugene, Oregon
      - Destroy the Humans!, Undated; Anarchy is Rad Collective (Box 12, Folder 70)
        Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada
      - Dig'em, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 81)
        Waterbury, Connecticut
      - Discords, 1981-09; Wuelfing, Howard S.M. (Box 7, Folder 10)
        Arlington, Virginia
      - Doctor Bong, 1985-04 (Box 2, Folder 82)
        Davis, California
      - Dodobobo, 1996-1999-08; Greene, Brian; Dodobobo Publications (Box 3, Folder 1)
        No. 10-11, 14, 17
      - Don't Make Trouble, 1991; Kupferberg, Tuli (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Donut Frenzy, 2000-2009; Upright, Andy (Box 3, Folder 3)
        No. 4 (2 copies), two unnumbered issues
        St. Paul, Minnesota; Philadelphia, Pennsylvania
      - Dreams of Donuts, 2014-01; Wreckage, Heather (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Drop Out, 1995-05; Pam (Box 12, Folder 71)
      - Drop Target, 2011-04-2014-08; Chad, Jon; Longstreth, Alec (Box 3, Folder 6)
        No. 2-6
        White River Junction, Vermont; Santa Fe, New Mexico
      - Duck, 1991; Travis (Box 3, Folder 7)
        Chico, California
    - Titles E-O, 1982-2013
      - Eggplant Place Comix, 1996; Dug (Box 12, Folder 72)
        Milwaukee, Wisconsin
      - Eleven, 1990; Olsen, Zeb (Box 12, Folder 73)
        North Sydney, Australia
      - Error, 1994-06; McPheeters, Sam (Box 8, Folder 2)
        No. 100
      - Etch, 1995; Knott, Ken; Zebrowski, Norman (Box 3, Folder 9)
        Lansing, Michigan
      - Existential Rage, 1980-1989; Steve (Box 3, Folder 10)
        No. 3.5
        Orange, California
      - Expletive Deleted, 2000; Cascadia Forest Defenders (Box 12, Folder 74)
      - FC, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 75)
      - Factsheet Five, 1985-02; Gunderloy, Michael A. (Box 3, Folder 11)
        No. 13
        Medford, Massachusetts
      - Fallout, 1984; Smith, Winston; Scotti, Jayed; Biafra, Jello (Box 7, Folder 12)
        Ukiah, California
      - Fanzine That-Had-No-Name, The, 1989-1990; Billig, Jamey (Box 3, Folder 12)
        Vol. 1 No. 1, Vol. 3 No. 1
        Santa Barbara, California
      - Feeding the Fowls, Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
        No. 1, 12
      - Feminist Baseball, 1992-05-1993-04; Smith, Jeff; Joyce, Craig (Box 3, Folder 14)
        No. 10-11
      - Feminist Carpetcleaner, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Femme Flicke, 1993-1994; Tina (Box 3, Folder 16)
        Allston, Massachusetts; Somerville, Massachusetts
      - Fight for Freedom, 1984; Vandal; Mish (Box 3, Folder 17)
        No. 15
        Long Beach, California
      - Finger on the Trigger, 2001-2003; R., Adee (Box 3, Folder 18)
        No. 1-5
        Pensacola, Florida; Lake Worth, Florida
      - Finster, 1988-1995; Mary; K.J.; Becca (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - Firefly, The, 1991-11-1994-05; Kirby, Jane; Lurie, Jon; Gemma (Box 3, Folder 20)
        No. 12, 17, 25
        Mission, South Dakota; Ely, Minnesota
      - First, Last, Security, 2008-01; Singer, Jessie; Roosevelt, Maura; Spies, Jonathan; Ryan, Kate; Eastwood, Corey; Alli, Sabrina; Aboaf, Jacques (Box 12, Folder 76)
      - Flake, 1992; Bruce, Scott (Box 3, Folder 21)
        No. 7-8
        Cambridge, Massachusetts
      - Flesh and Bones, 1983-09-1983-11; Jeff (Box 3, Folder 22)
        Includes note from editor
        Middlesex, New Jersey
      - Flesh and the Writing Table, 1998; Angie (Box 12, Folder 77)
        Columbus, Ohio
      - Flyer Flyer, The, Summer 1998; Smith, D.G. (Box 12, Folder 78)
        Bethesda, Maryland
      - Fuh Cole, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - Future is Now, The, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      - Get Loose, 1991-1995; Loose, Chuck (Box 3, Folder 25)
        No. 3, 5
        Boca Raton, Florida
      - Gingerboy, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 26)
        Portland, Oregon
      - Girl Gang, 1998; Fly (Box 3, Folder 27)
      - Girl Germs, 1991; Neuman, Molly; Wolfe, Allison (Box 12, Folder 79)
      - Girlhero, 1993-1996; Kelso, Megan; High Drive Publications (Box 12, Folder 80)
        No. 1-6
      - Glue, 1992-08; Jane (Box 3, Folder 28)
      - Good and Plenty, 1991-12-1992-02; Rodriguez, Gabe (Box 3, Folder 29)
        Zion, Illinois
      - Grade D But Edible, 1993-1994; Marko (Box 3, Folder 30)
        No. 13, 57
        Whitwell, Tennessee; Knoxville, Tennessee
      - Grand Canyon Stunt Double, 1993; Atkins, John (Box 12, Folder 81)
      - Gutter Butter, Undated; Burnhim, Badran (Box 3, Folder 31)
      - Hallelujaa, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 82)
        Tampere, Finland
      - Hamsterama, 1985-03-24; Rashkin, Elissa; Harris, Megan (Box 12, Folder 83)
        Pacific Grove, California
      - Harass the Brass, 2001; Keating, Kevin; Overground Distribution (Box 3, Folder 32)
      - Hatewagon, 1992-02-1993; Rebel, Lana (Box 3, Folder 33)
        No. 1, 3-4
        Tucson, Arizona
      - Heat Seeker, 1993-08; Romeo; Juliet (Box 3, Folder 34)
        Ashland, Oregon
      - Hellbound and Determined, 1988-07; Koenings, Torky (Box 12, Folder 84)
        Big Bear Lake, California
      - Hessian Obsession, 1991-1997; Quintner, John (Box 3, Folder 35)
      - Hippycore, 1988; Jack; Joel (Box 3, Folder 36)
        Mesa, Arizona
      - Houseless Journal, 1995-06; Reilly, Bridget (Box 12, Folder 85)
      - How to Use Tact and Skill in Handling People, 1994; Tonin, Sarah (Box 3, Folder 37)
      - Hungaro, 1992; Elvin, Michael R. (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - I Can't Explain, 1986-08-1986-09; Smith, Darius (Box 12, Folder 86)
        Oxford, Ohio
      - I'd Buy that for a Dollar, 1996-09-1999-02; G.M.; A.C.R.O.N.Y.M. Publishing (Box 3, Folder 39)
        No. 1-2, 4, 11
      - In the Van…Outta the Van, (Search for Food), 1988; Lage, Jen (Box 3, Folder 40)
        Downers Grove, Illinois
      - Incendiary Devices, 1991-05-01-1993 (Box 3, Folder 41)
        No. 3 (2 copies)
      - Jellybean State, Undated; Yates, John (Box 12, Folder 87)
        United Kingdom
      - Joe Prestons Legs AKA: Germ of Youth, 1992; Trosper, Justin (Box 12, Folder 88)
      - Killzine, 1986-08-17-1997; Romeo, Darby (Box 3, Folder 42)
      - King-Cat Comix & Stories, 2011-11-2013-11; Porcellino, John (Box 3, Folder 43)
        No. 72-74
        South Beloit, Illinois
      - La Pila, 1998-06; Engel, Richard (Box 12, Folder 89)
      - Last Rites, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 44)
        McHenry, Illinois
      - Late Afternoon Sun, 1994; Davis, Greg (Box 3, Folder 45)
      - Law and Disorder, Undated; Kringle, Chris (Box 12, Folder 90)
        Green Bay, Wisconsin
      - Leading Edge, 1983; Sprouse, Martin; Traeger, Jason (Box 3, Folder 46)
      - Leumas Komix, Undated; Sam; Chlorine Production (Box 3, Folder 47)
        Fields Landing, California
      - Life of Crime, 1987-07; Rashkin, Elissa (Box 3, Folder 48)
      - Little History of Every Car He's Ever Owned and All His Favorite Dogs Too, A, 1992; Fletcher, Harrell; Hilliard, Jess (Box 3, Folder 49)
        California
      - Little Free Press, 1985-04-1993; Mann, Ernest (Box 3, Folder 50)
        No. 50, 54(a, b, d), 77, 82, 86, 88-92, 116, 121-125, 129-131, 133-135, 137-138
        Minneapolis, Minnesota; Cushing, Minnesota; Little Falls, Minnesota
      - Loafing the Donkey, 1987-1988; Mantis, Peter (Box 3, Folder 51)
        Vol. 1 No. 9
        Royal Oak, Michigan
      - Lookout, 1984-02-1990-02; Livermore, Larry (Box 3, Folder 52)
        No. 14, 16, 25, 32, 34, and March 1987 special edition
        Laytonville, California
      - Lost Cause, Feb/Mar '94; Vagrant, Mike (Box 12, Folder 55)
        No. 2 (split with Bitch Magazine no. 7)
      - MCG Zine, 1985-05 (Box 12, Folder 91)
      - Maggots, 1996; Glowman, Glemun (Box 3, Folder 53)
        Providence, Rhode Island
      - Make-Out Session, Undated; Julie (Box 12, Folder 92)
        Atlanta, Georgia
      - Malice, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 54)
        No. 3, 7-8
        Memphis, Tennessee
      - Mangled Efforts, 1985; Kapell, Murray (Box 3, Folder 55)
      - Maximum Rock N' Paul, 1985-06-1985-08; Hamerlinck, Paul (Box 3, Folder 56)
        St. Cloud, Minnesota
      - Memphis Comics, 1982; Moriarty, R.B. (Box 3, Folder 57)
      - Mickey Rourke, 1993; Speen, Ray; Aloc Aloc Publications (Box 12, Folder 93)
        Iowa City, Iowa
      - Mikel, 1984-03 (Box 12, Folder 94)
        Vol. 2, No. 11
        Covina, California
      - Ministry of Truth, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 58)
        Nashville, Tennessee
      - Mission Statement, 1992; Rinaldo, Lucinda (Box 3, Folder 59)
        No. Q, V
        Wilton, Connecticut
      - Mom, 1993-1995; Pembleton, Lee; Terminal Projects Group (Box 3, Folder 60)
        Chicago, Illinois; Kodiak, Alaska
      - Monkeyshine, 1991-1992; Ben (Box 3, Folder 61)
      - Motherfucker, 1990-01 (Box 3, Folder 62)
      - Motorbooty, 1995-01-1995-02; Dancey (Box 3, Folder 63)
        Detroit, Michigan
      - Multiball, 1993; Coleman, Brinda; Soule, S.D. (Box 12, Folder 95)
      - Murmuring Memories, 1989-1993; Cia (Box 3, Folder 64)
        Garberville, California
      - Music Master, 1990-1999; Naomi (Box 3, Folder 65)
      - My Name is No, 2001; Mataro (Box 3, Folder 66)
      - My Town is on a Hill, 1995-07-14-1995-08-23; Sprout; Nora (Box 3, Folder 67)
        Warrensburg, Missouri
      - Nation of Two, Undated; Suh, James; Erin (Box 12, Folder 97)
        Part Two
        Ithaca, New York
        Ottawa, Ontario, Canada
      - Naughty Anti-Authoritarian Girls (N.A.A.G.), Undated (Box 3, Folder 68)
      - Negrita, 2001; Gloria (Box 3, Folder 69)
      - Neus Subjex, The, 2000-03 (Box 12, Folder 98)
        No. 29
        Fairfield, Ohio
      - New Found Friend, Undated; Dave; Matt (Box 12, Folder 99)
      - Nieuwe Koekrand, 1982-11-1985-08 (Box 3, Folder 70)
        No. 59, 69
      - Niffs Notes, 1997-12-08; Lookinland, Trick (Box 12, Folder 100)
        Carmichael, California
      - No Duh, 1991-12-1993; Farina, Geoff (Box 3, Folder 71)
        No. 1, 2 (2 copies), 4 (2 copies), 5, 6
        Allston, Massachusetts
      - No External Compulsion, 1995; T., Criterion (Box 12, Folder 101)
        No. 4-6
      - No Idea, 1987-1988-12; SR-10335; Thelin, Var (Box 3, Folder 72)
        Includes Crimpshrine/Mutley Chix 7" Record; No. 7
        Gainesville, Florida
      - Noise, 1997-12; Lasky, David (Box 12, Folder 102)
      - Noisemakers, 1993-1994; Myre, Ellen (Box 12, Folder 103)
      - Northbound 26, 1997-09; Maslowe, Lisa (Box 3, Folder 73)
        Seattle, Washington; New York, New York
      - Nosedive, 2003-06-2003-08; Apparatus, Icky (Box 3, Folder 74)
      - Not Always the News, 1991; Ralphy Boy (Box 12, Folder 104)
      - Now I…, 1993-1995; Ploeg, Joshua H. (Box 3, Folder 75)
      - Npp!, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 96)
        Kersberga, Sweden
      - Nuthin', 1997-1999; Sprout (Box 3, Folder 76)
      - O.C. Shitz, 1984; Reed, Mark; Chaz (Box 3, Folder 77)
        Garden Grove, California
      - Occupied Wall Street Journal, The, 2011-11; Brandt, Jed; Grim, Priscilla; Levitin, Michael; Rizzo, Ryan; Sacks, Jennifer (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Offense Newsletter, The, 1982-02-11-1986-07-04; Tim/TKA (Box 3, Folder 78)
        No. 1, 2, 14, 21, 45, 51, 62,67
      - Ooompa! Ooompa!, 1991-08-1993; Megan (Box 3, Folder 79)
        Allston, Massachusetts; Westerly, Rhode Island
      - OP, 1982-09-1982-10; Foster, John; Lost Music Network (Box 12, Folder 105)
        Issue "M"
      - OP, 1983-03-1983-04; Foster, John; Lost Music Network (Box 9, Folder 24)
        Issue "P"
      - Opera Vagabond, The, 1996-03 (Box 3, Folder 80)
        Ontario, Canada; Matawan, New Jersey
      - Organ, 1989; Wipfli, Sean (Box 12, Folder 106)
      - Ouchcube!, Undated; Goodrich, David; Clarke, Christopher; Pizzuro, Steve; Clarke, Glenda (Box 12, Folder 107)
        Vol. 1, No. 1
      - Our Flag is Black, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 81)
      - Outer Shell, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 82)
        Vol. 10
        St. Petersburg Florida
      - Overground Distribution catalog, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 83)
      - Over the Edge, 1990; Luevano, Adan (Box 3, Folder 84)
        Flagstaff, Arizona
    - Titles P-Z, 1978-2013
      - Patch, 1990-1996; Patch, Brian (Box 3, Folder 85)
        No. 3-6
        Richmond, Virginia; Dade City, Florida
      - Peeked Zine, 1992; R., Achille; W., Steve (Box 12, Folder 108)
      - Pen Pals, 1984; Nishit, Nina (Box 12, Folder 109)
        Boise, Idaho
      - Peops, 2010-2014; Fly (Box 3, Folder 86)
        No. 5-7, 8 (2 copies), 8.9
      - Phoenix and Reveloooooshun of None, 1992; Rico (Box 3, Folder 87)
        No. 2 No. 1
      - Pig Paper, The, 1982; Pig Productions (Box 3, Folder 88)
        No. 26, 28
        Ontario, Canada
      - Pills, 2002-11; Snakepit, Ben; Snakepit Comix (Box 3, Folder 89)
      - Ping Throng!, 1990-11; Rebel, Lana; Emily (Box 3, Folder 90)
      - Pipeline Fanzine, 1984; Tim; Society Reject Music (Box 12, Folder 110)
        Highland, Illinois
      - Plotz, 1997-1999; Barbara (Box 3, Folder 91)
        No. 8, 11
      - Pocket Quik Politics, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 111)
        Saint Paul, Minnesota
      - Point of Interest, 1991; Jay (Box 12, Folder 112)
      - Poison Briggs, 1983; Bevan, Julian (Box 3, Folder 92)
        Cincinnati, Ohio
      - Pollution Control, 1983-1984; Pennie (Box 3, Folder 93)
      - Pop Lust, 1984-01-1984-02; Morgan, Rob (Box 3, Folder 94)
      - Portion of Existence, 1998-09-22; Zenick, Jeff (Box 3, Folder 95)
      - Portland, Undated (Box 3, Folder 96)
      - Precautions Essentielles pour la Bonne, 1981; Vicious, Julian; Pete (Box 3, Folder 97)
        London, England
      - Primal Scream, 1985; Mendes, Cindy (Box 3, Folder 98)
      - Psalm 151, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
        Denver, Colorado
      - Psychotherapy, 1991-1992; Prodoehl, Pete (Box 4, Folder 2)
        No. 13-15
      - Puddles of Blood, 1984-1986; Gonzalez, David (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Pulp, 1990-1991; Chris (Box 4, Folder 4)
        No. 3, 6
      - Punk in My Vitamins?, 1992-1993-08; Vern (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Push-Button Controller, 1991-03-1992-05; Gordon, Ben (Box 4, Folder 6)
        Glenville, New York
      - Quickdraw, 1996; Weeks, John (Box 4, Folder 7)
        Victoria, Australia
      - Rad Party, 2000-2010-02; Stephane (Box 4, Folder 8)
        No. 41, 43
        France
      - Radio Riot, 1991-11-1993-01; Gard, Mat (Box 4, Folder 9)
        No. 5, 18-19
        New Brunswick, New Jersey
      - Ralph, 1993-12-1996-02; Alfonso, Ralph (Box 4, Folder 10)
        No. 13, 19, 36
      - Ramen City U.S.A., 1994-1998; Sierra; Hank (Box 4, Folder 11)
        No. 7, 9, 12, 14
        Eugene, Oregon; Szeged, Hungary
      - Ratlanta, 1985-12; Hoffman, Vince (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Rattlesnake Press, 1991; Pete (Box 12, Folder 113)
        No. 1-5, 11 (on verso of Snakebite zine)
      - Real Fun, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 13)
        Philadelphia, Pennsylvania
      - Reality Control?, 1990-1992; Lyons, John (Box 4, Folder 14)
        Carpinteria, California
      - Revealin' Da Lies, 1983; Omlit, Robert (Box 4, Folder 15)
        No. 1.
        Donor's note: Omlit is an exciting, important, and overlooked historical figure in the developement of Orange County Punk
      - Revenge Against Boredom, 1983-04; Weyland, John (Box 4, Folder 16)
        Estes Park, Colorado
      - Ride On!, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 114)
        Includes interview with Aaron Cometbus
        Abington, Pennsylvania
      - Ring of Fire, 1996-1997; Homosex, Hellery (Box 4, Folder 17)
      - Roessiger, 1991; Green, Ryan (Box 4, Folder 18)
      - Round Things Roll, 2001; Williams, Allison (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - Rump, 1992-1993; Haeg, Mike (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - Saint Cards I Found in Her Purse, 2007; Llosa-Sandor, Tamara (Box 4, Folder 21)
        New England
      - Saprophile, 1992-08-1993-03; Landmark, Eric (Box 4, Folder 22)
      - Sassiest Girl in America, 1994-09 (Box 4, Folder 23)
      - Second Guess, 1992-09-1994; C., Bob (Box 4, Folder 24)
        No. 4, 11
        Reno, Nevada
      - Second Set Out, 2003-05; Bowstern, Moe (Box 4, Folder 25)
      - Secret Asian Man, 1997; M. (Box 4, Folder 26)
      - Sexy, 1990; Moeller, Kate (Box 12, Folder 115)
        Seymour, Wisconsin
      - Shebang, Undated; Angulo, Omar (Box 12, Folder 116)
        Miami, Florida
      - Shithappy, 1991-1994; Bregman, Adam (Box 4, Folder 27)
        No. 2-4
      - Shoot, 1983-1985; Schneck, Carol (Box 4, Folder 28)
        No. 4, 8
      - Sick Teen, 1980-1993; Ugly, Rev. Norb (Box 4, Folder 29)
      - Six Foot Crow, 1992-04; Crow, Alex; Dr. Nefarious (Box 12, Folder 117)
        Dallas, Texas
      - Skid, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 30)
        Oconomowoc, Wisconsin
      - Skinny, 1997-01-20-1997-04-14; Persinger, Silver; Farrell, Mike (Box 12, Folder 118)
        No. 2-3, 5-6, 9, 11-12
      - Slop Hut, 1994-1995; Steven (Box 4, Folder 32)
      - Smegma, 1987-10; Smeg (Box 4, Folder 33)
        Livingston, California
      - Smell of Dead Fish, The, 1986-1997; Cowgill, Skott (Box 4, Folder 34)
        No. 12, 13, 15, 18, 25, 30, 35, 47-48
      - Smell of Steve Spotlight on: The Homeless, 1994; S., Brian (Box 4, Folder 35)
        Vol. 0 No. 1
      - Smoke en la Boca, 1996; Jessie (Box 12, Folder 119)
        Helena, Montana
      - Smokin' Cigarettes & Drinkin' Coffee, 1989; Aldini, Jerry; Clint (Box 4, Folder 36)
        No. 2, 6/42
        Grand Prairie, Texas
      - Snackbar Confidential, Undated; Dribbleman, Willard (Box 12, Folder 120)
        Saratoga Springs, New York
      - Snakebite, 1991; Bessa, Kelly (Box 12, Folder 113)
        No. 1, 2, 4, 5, 11 (on verso of Rattlesnake Press zine)
      - Snakepit, 2003; Ben (Box 4, Folder 37)
        No. 27.5, 28
      - Snipehunt, 1995-06-1995-08 (Box 9, Folder 4)
        No. 24
      - Sociopath, 2001; Racine, Mike (Box 4, Folder 38)
      - Something for Nothing, 1998-2018; Idy (Box 4, Folder 39)
        No. 38, 40 (supplement), 61, 64, 67-68, 71, 75
        Massillon, Ohio
      - Sound Off, 1992; Gatewood, Dan (Box 4, Folder 40)
      - Sound Views, 1992-08; Greenfeld, Lee (Box 4, Folder 41)
        Brooklyn Heights, New York
      - Southern Lifestyle, 1985; James (Box 9, Folder 5)
        No. 11, Vol. 11 No. 2 (2 copies)
        Raleigh, North Carolina
      - Spaghetti Dinner & Dancing, 1999-07-2000; Spaghetti, Randy (Box 4, Folder 42)
        No. 13-14
        Missoula, Montana
      - Spitshine the Eye, Undated; Jen (Box 4, Folder 43)
      - Splatterspleen, 1996; Amanda (Box 4, Folder 44)
      - Sporadic Droolings, 1986; Burokas, Dave (Box 4, Folder 45)
        Kearny, New Jersey
      - Stop!, 1983-04-1983-05; King, J.D.; Holmstrom, John (Box 4, Folder 46)
      - Strand Bookstore Labor Dispute Comics, 2012-04; Farrell, Greg (Box 4, Folder 47)
      - Student Insurgent, The, 1995-04-12; Brady, Chris (Box 8, Folder 5)
        Vol. 6 No. 11
      - Sty, 1995-03-1995-05; Icky (Box 8, Folder 6)
        No. 20
        Bloomington, Indiana
      - Sub Cin, 1984-05; Fits, Tim (Box 4, Folder 48)
      - Suburban Voice, 1985; Quint, Al (Box 4, Folder 49)
        No. 16
        Swampscott, Massachusetts
      - Suicidiary, 1993-1995; Terminal Projects Group (Box 4, Folder 50)
        Vol. 1, 3, 5, 6, 8-10, 12
        Kodiak, Alaska; Orem, Utah
      - Sweet Ride, The, 1987-1990; Russell, Randy; Legal Hassle Publications; T.B.S. Publications (Box 4, Folder 51)
        No. 8, 9, 13-14
        Sandusky, Ohio; Cleveland, Ohio
      - Surreptitious, Undated; Sprout (Box 12, Folder 121)
        Vol. 8
      - Take It!, 1981; Koenig, Michael; Barone, Salvatore (Box 9, Folder 25)
      - Talking Back to Walt Whitman, Undated (Box 4, Folder 52)
      - Teabag, The, 1995; Patch, Brian (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - Terminal!, 1983; Fritz, Steven; Schutzbank, Carol (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Testube, 1985; Hunker, Tracy (Box 9, Folder 9)
        Vol. 2-4 (2 copies)
      - Texas, 1997-1998; Alan (Box 12, Folder 122)
        Northampton, United Kingdom
      - Things are Cooking at the Phallic Silo, 1981-1989 (Box 4, Folder 54)
      - Third Rail, 1985-12-12 (Box 4, Folder 55)
        Stillwater, Oklahoma
      - This is Not a Travel Journal, 1995-08; Davis, P. (Box 12, Folder 123)
      - This Is What I Heard, Undated; Kim; Ann (Box 4, Folder 56)
      - Three, 1993; Leumas (Box 4, Folder 57)
      - Thrill!, 1990; Brad; Jeff; Sean; Crayon (Box 4, Folder 58)
        Bellingham, Washington
      - Trends, 1908-04; Mob Policy (Box 4, Folder 59)
        Bolton, United Kingdom
      - Trouser Press, 1981-07 (Box 4, Folder 60)
        Vol. 8 No. 5 (63)
      - Truly Needy, 1983-1985; Rice, Barbara (Box 4, Folder 61)
        Vol. 2 No. 3 (No. 7), Vol. 2 No. 5 (No. 8)
        Rockville, Maryland; Washington, D.C.
      - Twenty Five Reasons, 1998; Reasons, Jayson (Box 4, Folder 62)
      - Twin Cities Lard Gore, 1990-07-29; AYF (Box 4, Folder 63)
        No. 1 (2 copies)
      - Typograpunx, Undated; Palmer, David (Box 12, Folder 124)
        Bel Air, Maryland
      - Unscene, The, 2001-02 (Box 12, Folder 125)
      - Untitled, 1993-05 (Box 4, Folder 64)
      - Upper Left Edge, 1993-06 (Box 8, Folder 7)
        Vol. 2, No. 3
        Cannon Beach, Oregon
      - Urgl-Orp, 1984-11; Nicole (Box 4, Folder 65)
        No. 8.5
      - Urinal, The, 1990-09-1991; Farrell, Mike (Box 4, Folder 66)
      - Verboslammed, 1995-01-1996-01; Rebecca (Box 4, Folder 67)
        No. 7, 8
      - Void, 1989-1991; Boyde (Box 4, Folder 68)
      - W. D. C. Period, 1986-03-1987-02; Ornelas, Gordon; Chow Chow Productions (Box 9, Folder 12)
        No. 14-16
      - Wake Up, 1986; Ramona (Allen, Beth) (Box 4, Folder 69)
      - Walkie Talkie, 2002-01; Powell, Nate (Box 4, Folder 70)
        Little Rock, Arkansas
      - Warm Orchid, Undated; Green, Kelly; Farrell, Don; Aerol, Meg; Longacre, Barton; Savoie, Ryan; Dickinson, Paul D.; Marsenich, Milana (Box 12, Folder 126)